Edid, Maralyn Collection of Xerox Corporation Labor-Management Relations Papers 6264
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Maralyn Edid Collection of Xerox Corporation Labor-Management Relations Papers
1980- 2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Edid, Maralyn
6264
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Papers.
6308569
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 07, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6263: Maralyn Edid Collection of Migrant Farm Workers Publications 6265: Maralyn Edid Collection of National Partnership Council Papers
Industrial relations; Edid, Maralyn, 1950-; Xerox Corporation
6308569
- ACTWU/Xerox. Past Present Future: The Journey of Choice., 1980-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Building 223. Photo Plant Stratagy for Empowerment. [sic], 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Business Area Work Group., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Business Center Steering Committee., 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- CMO/FUSER. Plant Advisory Committee Agenda. 11Jul96., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- International Work Groups., 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ISO 14001 Overview. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- MEM. Self Directed Work Team. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- UNITE/Xerox. Joint Process Strategic Architecture., 1980-2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- WMO News. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Scope and Contents
  v.1:no.3.
- Workplace Change Study. (Box 1, Folder 11)